https://adriangrimm.com

Profile

I am a passionate front-end developer that focuses on writing idiomatic, scalable and accessible code while prioritizing teamwork and collaboration with others as a part of my workflow. My primary experience and skills are API Design, React, AWS, modern GitHub practices and accessibility.

Education

Vets Who Code, remote - Completed program, 2020

 Completed coursework on Accessibility, React, Git, GraphQL, AWS, Algorithms and Data Structures

Stark State College - Certification, 2020

• Completed coursework on SQL, HTML/CSS, Bootstrap, WordPress Development

Experience

Open Source Contributor, Vets Who Code - 2020-Present

Here I perform open source contributions to get real world experience working with technical teams. I have pair programmed with the team to implement several features, particularly the lambdas that handle forms.

Securitas Electronic Security and Diebold, Inc - 2012 - Present

While here I perform the technical duties to support technicians in the field perform their duties flawlessly for our customers. I utilized and maintained an SQL database for our team to create new users for access management as well as report generation.

United States Marine Corps, 2002 - 2010

During my tenure in the United States Marine Corps I trained, mentored, and supervised new Marines, managed \$5.2 billion worth of assets, created the strategy and planned the physical and digital security of important officials, and was promoted into senior leadership roles.